{"test_questions": [[{"question": "An action assertion must include which of the following?", "opta": "Anchor object", "optb": "Action", "optc": "Corresponding object", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An oval represents which of the following in an EER?", "opta": "Attribute", "optb": "Entity", "optc": "Optional One", "optd": "Relationship", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Inheritance is which of the following?", "opta": "When a supertype entity inherits values of the subtype attribute", "optb": "When a subtype entity inherits values of the supertype attribute", "optc": "When a supertype entity inherits values of another supertype attribute", "optd": "When a subtype entity inherits values of another subtype attribute", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When an entity instance must be a member of only one subtype, it is which of the following?", "opta": "Disjoint with total specialization", "optb": "Disjoint with partial specialization", "optc": "Overlap with total specialization", "optd": "Overlap with partial specialization", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A supertype/subtype hierarchy is which of the following?", "opta": "Each subtype has only one attribute.", "optb": "Each supertype has only one attribute.", "optc": "Each subtype has only one supertype.", "optd": "Each supertype has only one subtype.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A rectangle represents which of the following in an EER?", "opta": "Attribute", "optb": "Entity", "optc": "Optional One", "optd": "Relationship", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which one of the following symbols is not used in an ERD?", "opta": "Rectangle", "optb": "Oval", "optc": "Diamond", "optd": "Circle", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Specialization is which of the following processes?", "opta": "Defining one or more subtypes of the supertype and forming supertype/subtype relationships.", "optb": "Defining one or more supertypes of the subtype and forming supertype/subtype relationships.", "optc": "Defining one or more subtypes of the supertype and not forming supertype/subtype relationships.", "optd": "Defining one or more supertypes of the subtype and not forming supertype/subtype relationships.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following statements concerning business rules is true?", "opta": "It should be complex.", "optb": "It should not be convertible to computer code.", "optc": "It may include restrictions.", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A supertype/subtype hierarchy has which of the following features?", "opta": "Subtypes at the lower lever in the hierarchy inherit attributes only from their immediate supertype.", "optb": "Attributes are assigned at the highest logical level.", "optc": "Subtypes at the higher lever in the hierarchy inherit attributes only from their immediate subtype.", "optd": "Attributes are assigned at the lowest logical level.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A subtype discriminator is which of the following?", "opta": "An attribute of the supertype whose values determine the subtype", "optb": "An attribute of the subtype whose values determine the supertype", "optc": "An attribute of the supertype whose values determine the supertype", "optd": "An attribute of the subtype whose values determine the subtype", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When an entity instance may be a member of multiple subtypes or it does not have to be a member of a subtype, it is which of the following?", "opta": "Disjoint with total specialization", "optb": "Disjoint with partial specialization", "optc": "Overlap with total specialization", "optd": "Overlap with partial specialization", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A subtype entity name should be which of the following?", "opta": "A singular noun", "optb": "Specific to the organization", "optc": "Concise", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Use of a supertype/subtype relationship is necessary when which of the following exists?", "opta": "An instance of a subtype participates in a relationship that is unique to that subtype.", "optb": "An instance of a subtype participates in a relationship that is the same as the other subtypes.", "optc": "Attributes apply to all of the instances of an entity type.", "optd": "No attributes apply to any of the instances of an entity type.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is not one of the three ways to classify an action assertion?", "opta": "Condition", "optb": "Integrity Control", "optc": "Authorization", "optd": "Enabler", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}